Today it's going to be sparkly and full of glitter because I have pieces from
Laurent Lajos from Munich. A glamour accessories designer and we have a whole
ensemble in red and some dresses, catsuits, bodysuits which are like
see-through but with a lot of rhinestones. Starting with the red set I
I have several pieces and it's going to be a whole look.
So I have to change.
Ta-da!
This is the whole set.
I paired it with a black simple catsuit to make the red really pop and stand out.
And also because we're here on YouTube.
But I plan to do a photoshoot next week without the black catsuit.
Anyway, I think this is just a gorgeous outfit.
It consists of several pieces. We have the shoulders here, a bra part, the belt, the panty, choker, wristlets or bracelets and this leg accessory. I just attached it to the panty but let me take it off to show you.
You can also put it on every kind of jeans or other kind of pants.
And here you can see again how cool the sparkle is.
And the details are really nice with the old chains and rivets.
We have some red sparkly rivets here too.
Really nice.
Since there are so many pieces you can mix and match basically. You can just wear an outfit with the shoulders and put it on top of something else.
Or you could just wear the choker. They have different colors so check out their shop because I will link it down below and you'll find everything there.
I think the way I overlap the pieces it kind of looks like armor but also like
something spacey due to shoulders here and let me take off the shoulders so as
I said you can put them on top of every kind of outfit it's just to give it some
extra pop and without the shoulders the outfit is a bit more plain you can maybe
imagine it without the catsuit so it's more kind of a lingerie outfit now
totally fine for queer events fetish parties everywhere you want to stand out
because this is just so sparkly these are ready-made pieces I wearing size
small but when I met Laurent and Franz the two owners they were doing a fashion
show at the Avant-gardista in Munich last year and they had incredible show
pieces so I was like if you send me something for the video please send
along something from your show whoops so I'm going to switch into that catsuit
now which doesn't want to stay on the hanger obviously the catsuit I haven't
checked myself in the mirror yet so I'm going to do that. Oh my gosh this is amazing. It's so sparkly
and it's still kind of black and a bit of coffee vibe with the mesh but the sparkle is really
really accentuating the body shape like more the boobies here and with the line
here on the side that has no rhinestones so it elongates the body kind of so I
just I think it's really really nice catsuit also the back here that we have
like skin going on but then the choker part the neck part whatever so I love
this I'm so glad I said please send me one of your show outfits because I saw
them in the showroom at Avancadista and I was like oh my god this looks so great
I love it and now that I'm wearing it yes I definitely love it
just have to keep checking the mirror again because there's so much to see
with all the stones and glitter and the shapes worked into the stones. Nice! I mean
yeah you could for a party wear it without underwear maybe then would be
really revealing so I'm not going to do that here but yeah check out their
homepage I think they have a lot of pictures online from when they worked
with celebrities or different shows and just write them an email if you're
interested in something like this now for the next outfit I do have a bodysuit and a cloak
and I think I'll put them together and see how it looks so this is the bodysuit on itself
I love that we have a front zipper here so I like to have it open just to show some neckline but
I could also close it like this. Though I think with this cut this looks better. I have to hide my
bra straps a bit more. Anyway the back side is completely full of rhinestones and the front as
well and as I said I have a cloak that I'm going to put on top because I hope
it's going to look good
yes so it's closed now and I mean this is a show outfit like imagine that on a catwalk
which they did in Munich and I saw it and it was awesome
kind of reminds me of the invisibility cloak from Harry Potter
it's fun you could also wear something really plain underneath even a catsuit and you would
light up the outfit just with that cloak i love it i feel like a child again
that put like a blanket on its shoulders but this one is way more glamorous
okay and for the last outfit I do have a dress which I have to put on over my head so I will
see how that goes with hair and makeup so we're taking some selfies I realized there are armholes
in the cloak there has to be one on this side too yeah I didn't even notice with all the fabric
going on that now you have some kind of poncho I don't know and it's definitely
more handy this way because you can use your hands now this is right up my alley
a cute little black dress mesh and a lot of glitter and partially the glitter is
even black so it's nice and yeah not too colorful so to say and I just love the
type of dress now I say glitter all the time but of course these are rhinestones
maybe some kind of small rivets and of course hand applied so hours and hours
of work that went into the dress, the catsuit, the bodysuit, the cloak. Mind-blowing.
So yeah, just love this dress. I like all the outfits. I think the red ensemble was
really awesome and this would be my second place. And then followed by the catsuit.
But I mean catsuit and dress are kind of a tie
Because it depends on your mood if you want to wear a dress or catsuit
Anyway, check out La Rola Yos
Thanks guys for sending these things over to me so I can present them to my YouTube
followers and audience because I think
Yeah, it's a new it's a young label. You should check it out. They make awesome stuff and I
Look awesome in it
Anyway, this was it for today. I hope you enjoyed it and leave a thumbs up. I will see
you in the next video. Bye!